Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
HEROES NEXT DOOR
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
ALL CHARACTERS, PROFESSIONS, PLACES,
COMPANIES, ORGANIZATIONS,
ETHNIC GROUPS AND EVENTS ARE NOT REAL.
ALL CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED
SAFELY UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION.
MINISTER OF NATIONAL DEFENSE: KIM SEOK-JUN
CYBER OPERATIONS COMMAND:
BRIGADIER GENERAL KIM DO-HYEONG, UNIT 900
LOGISTIC SUPPORT GROUP COMMANDER:
COLONEL JANG JUN-HUI
If it's a modified Composition C-4...
DEFENSE ACQUISITION PROGRAM ADMINISTRATOR:
KANG JUNG-GI
It's definitely the bomb
we snuck away then.
I know, I'm looking at it right now!
Why point out the obvious?
Am I asking you if the bomb belongs to us?
I'm asking what it's doing out there!
Have you checked the inventory count?
Yes, and the said bomb
isn't used in the military anymore.
The ones used last time
were classified as mission supplies.
Exactly. We exported all of them abroad.
So, how did an exported bomb
make a U-turn and return to Korea?
Maybe there was
an issue with the delivery.
They paid us the right amount.
That means they definitely got the goods.
Could it be...
an act of terrorism?
Had that been the case,
the terrorists would've come forward,
demanding something!
And why would any terrorist organization
want to target Kiyun-si?
It's not even Seoul!
You're so thick-headed.
Listen up.
Whatever it is,
make sure the guys
who were at the site stay quiet.
Keep a good eye on them.
If this goes wrong,
it's over for all of us. Got it?
- Yes, sir.
- Tell all the ones on leave to return.
Yes, sir.
Cyber Operations Command,
Logistics Support Group,
and the Defense Acquisition Program
Administrator?
What were they doing together?
MY BESTIE'S BESTIE IS MY BESTIE TOO
YOU'RE MAKING THINGS COMPLICATED
JDD SPECIAL OPERATIONS FORCES, CHOI KANG
They know me?
Does this unit actually exist?
Are you really from the JDD unit?
I've never heard
of the JDD Special Operations Forces.
- You know the Jindo Dog Alert? So--
- Wait.
- Look at this.
- At what?
Look at this.
"A new day is...
coming"?
A NEW DAY IS COMING
It shut down.
What's going on? What happened?
It's completely shut down.
Why? Did you break it?
So, what now?
"A new day is coming"?
What does that mean?
How should I know?
I'm just reading what's on the screen.
I can read, too, you know?
What I want to ask is--
Mr. Choi, get changed first.
Thank you.
Are you sure you're fine?
Are you sure you're not hurt badly
under your shirt?
I'm fine.
I told you not to follow me.
I mean, we also need to see
what happened...
What?
He definitely died.
They cleaned it up so quickly.
Do they have a cleanup crew with them?
What is this? I don't see anyone.
Are you sure you fought someone here?
Are you sure
that's not chili powder and ketchup?
Try tasting it, then.
You think I'm that bored?
My gosh!
- What?
It's so clean.
I've never seen these urinals this clean!
Man!
You're right.
Damn.
Are you kidding me?
How do we check the security cameras
in the hallway and the exit?
The management office.
That's odd. Is the memory full?
Why did it not record anything only here?
Someone seems to have tampered with it.
They would've gotten rid of it all.
That quickly?
You're saying they cleaned the bathroom
and took care of the security cameras too?
These guys are pros.
They seem to have
a cleanup crew with them.
A cleanup crew?
To clean up after all the mess?
I should've just walked away
when he mentioned North Korean spies.
Let's report it to the police first.
What will we tell them?
That you beat someone up
on your way to take a dump?
We need to leave a record of it
in case we get blamed later.
Good point.
Hey, contact Officer Park.
No, call the police hotline.
An informal report to an officer won't do.
Okay, but what should we say?
That you went to take a dump
and beat someone up?
Hey. Don't mention the dump.
What if they ask
why he went to the bathroom?
Tell me more about the JDD unit.
Is it real?
- Is there really such a unit in Korea?
- Exactly.
No comment.
Oh, you can't tell us?
That means it's real.
JDD? Is it short for "Jindo dog"?
No comment.
I heard you're only deployed
on high-risk combat missions.
Not even other military units know of it.
And it doesn't belong
to the Ministry of National Defense.
Are these all true?
That's incredible.
Where did you hear all that?
Who discusses state secrets so openly?
No comment, okay? Stop asking me about it.
Yes, sir.
Sure, whatever.
Right. What are you going to do with that?
- What's your plan?
- Oh, this?
I thought about reporting it to the cops,
but I missed my time to do it.
We can give it to them,
but let's check the files in it first.
And please get me a copy of the footage
of the accident at the intersection.
Great idea. You can do it, right?
They used a remote control
to factory reset the settings.
But I'll try it.
I'll set up the equipment today.
Okay, goodnight, then.
Okay.
- Goodnight, Mr. Choi!
- Goodnight.
Man... He really is from JDD.
Everything makes sense now,
with the gun and all.
So, he's the Jason Bourne of Korea.
Amazing.
He's much scarier than we thought.
Look at how they recognized him
immediately.
Choi Kang, look at what you've done to us.
- Byeong-nam.
- Yeah?
Isn't it better for us
that we have him on our side?
What is this? A soccer match? What side?
But he's definitely not
on the other side, right?
Of course not!
Enough with the pointless doubts!
Hey, you're always on the computer,
hacking or whatever,
but you were so useless earlier.
I wouldn't have expected
any more from you.
They suddenly started
remote-controlling it,
and I've never seen this laptop model!
- Sure.
- I was just confused, okay?
Sure, you were.
- Hey.
- What?
I'll look into it, but you can take it.
I can't put the kids at my gym at risk.
You can't put the kids at risk,
but I'm okay?
Give it.
- And Byeong-nam.
- What now?
Invite Mr. Choi
to the hardware store from now on.
Man, where are your balls?
Seriously.
Fine. Go now.
I'm also walking that way.
Oh, right. Come.
SPECIAL MARTIAL ARTS
Honey, what are you doing there?
I was just going to the bathroom.
You took a while.
Yeah, I did a loop
around the neighborhood.
Go back to sleep.
"Yongmu Gym"?
Don't put it in the laundry inside out.
Okay, just go to bed already.
Are you a foreigner?
Watch out!
Who sent you here? Tell me.
"A new day is coming"?
MAMMOSEU MART
Min-seo, cut it out.
I'm the only one
among my friends without it.
I'll study really hard.
Just get me this, please?
Please, Mom.
Wake up.
What middle-school student
wears sneakers that cost 500,000 won?
Don't you see your mom and dad
working to the bone here?
Take this.
- But Mom.
- Gosh.
You don't need to call me that so loudly.
The whole town knows I'm your mom already.
Are you really not getting them for me?
No, you can save the money
and get a pair for yourself.
- You're so mean.
- Whatever.
Was I adopted?
You think adopting is easy?
That costs money, you know?
Goodness.
- Hello.
- Hey, Myeong-o.
What's with Min-seo?
What's with the butane gas?
Oh, these.
You know the butane gas
that exploded in the ATM?
- They're recalling them all.
- I see.
Your first day at work
is coming soon, isn't it?
Yes.
Your mom is over the moon
because you work for a big company now.
She said she'd host a party
for the Women's Association.
My gosh, Mom.
Why shouldn't she?
If Min-seo went to Hanguk University
and got a good job like you,
I'd host a party for the entire town
with a whole pig and a cow.
I'd be practically
dancing around the streets.
But look at her.
She just asked if she was adopted
just because I wouldn't buy her sneakers.
Min-seo is smart.
Jeong-hwan said she was a quick learner
with great comprehension skills.
He never lies.
- Really?
- Of course.
Anyway, thanks for introducing me
to such a great tutor.
It's nothing.
- I'll get going now.
- Okay.
- Have a good day.
- You, too.
Of course.
It's impossible for her to be stupid
if she takes after me.
This is better than I expected.
You'll get the basics down soon.
Why didn't you try hard in school
when you're so smart?
I'm complimenting you. Why the long face?
Sullivan credits his parents
for all his success.
His birth parents abandoned him,
but his adoptive parents
gave him everything.
He said he got a second chance at life,
thanks to being adopted,
which eventually led him to success.
Did you save up your own money
to get your car?
No, my parents helped me.
My mom wants me to save up
and buy my own sneakers.
By the way,
do you have a girlfriend?
No.
That's why studying
is my biggest interest nowadays.
I don't know why I haven't tried harder
with such a smart brain.
Should I move on to the next question?
Sure, here's your pen.
Honey.
You got changed?
Where are you going now?
The youth association president
wants to see me.
I'll be right back.
What youth association president?
It's the hardware store owner.
He looks too old to be a youth, though.
Anyway, the owner of the grocery store
is the head of the Women's Association,
and the owner of the laundry place is
the head of the neighborhood association.
What an organized neighborhood, right?
Anyway, see you.
It's dangerous out today,
so stay home with Do-yeon, okay?
What's dangerous?
The micro dusts.
The pollution level is crazy today.
It's life-threatening.
See you.
Why are you going out, then?
Why?
Here.
If this is an assassination attempt,
you should've chosen the right poison.
I'm very immune.
Not just any poison gets to me.
Do they train you
for assassination attempts at JDD?
There's no such training. Come on, man.
You're the one who mentioned
all that about being immune.
I was just trying to be nice.
So why are you suddenly being nice?
Of course I'll get suspicious.
And all Korean dads are immune.
From eating all the food
their kids drop on the floor.
Whatever.
I served in the HID unit
until I had to transfer
to the Maintenance Battalion.
Okay, whatever.
Let me just ask you one thing.
How old are you, Mr. Hardware?
Me?
I was a freshman in 1998.
What? So was I.
Born in the year of the sheep?
No way!
I didn't expect to meet
someone my age in my neighborhood.
Hey, buddy. Nice to meet you.
You're changing the topic.
You're younger than me, aren't you?
Who changed the topic? You did, not me.
Whatever.
Tell me more about the JDD unit.
You know what acid the army can't handle?
An acid the army can't handle?
Nitric acid? No.
No, sulfuric acid.
Amino acid!
Army-no acid! You know?
You can't make your whole personality
about serving without even knowing this.
Are you sure you're from the HID unit?
Where's the gun? I have to shoot you.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, honey.
Where are you, Daddy?
Hey, my cutie.
I'm just out for a bit.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Come to the street pub at the intersection
after dinner tonight.
I'm grabbing a drink with the guys.
You should get to know your neighbors.
Aren't I right, buddy?
Let me ask you a favor.
Let's not talk about the no comment thing
around others, all right?
Sure, friend.
- Cheers!
He's one of us now, okay?
- Sure.
- Yes, pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
Feels like you're one of us already.
I like you now a lot better than
when you were acting up at the hospital.
- What's your name? Choi...
- Choi Kang.
You look so gentle,
yet your name means "the strongest."
What a strong boy.
I don't know about anything else,
but my name never loses.
I have a name women quite like, too.
You know "Kim Su-il's diamond," right?
I used to seduce women
by promising a fist-sized diamond.
Who'd understand
the "Kim Su-il's diamond" reference now?
Do you even know how much diamonds cost?
You know how much a fist-sized one is?
You have no idea, do you?
- Why don't I take that fist
- My gosh.
and break all your teeth?
Sorry that things have been chaotic
since you moved.
We rarely have incidents like these.
Things were great around here
when the housing prices skyrocketed
after the specialized zone announcement.
Kang, how old are you?
Around Byeong-nam's age?
Yeah, we were freshmen in college
in the same year.
We're the same age.
Then born in the year of the monkey?
So you're also 12 years younger than me.
I was born in the year of the sheep.
Little Byeong-nam here may look rough,
but he can be quite cute.
Stop it. All my friends
were born in the year of the sheep.
And we're friends
if we were freshmen in the same year.
Sure, kiddo. I'll let it slide.
Have a drink, little bro.
He was born in the year of the monkey.
- Whatever.
- Here you go.
Hey, we haven't gotten together
since that night.
- Right.
- Ji-hun.
You were also here
on the night of the accident.
Yeah, I had to stay here until sunrise
to clean up at the pub.
- You must've been scared, too.
- I was scared out of my mind.
- Enjoy.
- Okay.
Goodness.
So Byeong-nam has an early birthday?
Give me a moment.
Excuse me.
Did you happen to see
the driver of the other car,
not the truck?
I don't know
about the driver of the other car.
But a tow truck came
when the firefighters put out the fire.
And the tow truck just took that car.
Do you remember
the color of the tow truck or its company?
No, I don't.
Anything else?
You must've seen something
since you stayed here all night.
Oh, right.
And a 2.5t truck came
and cleaned up the site.
Judging by their light packs,
they seemed like the standby squad.
A 2.5t truck? You mean a military truck?
Yeah, I know it because
I drove one as a military driver.
They looked like
the Logistic Support Group.
Back in the day, they specialized
in flood and forest fire recovery,
so I was surprised to see them
clean up after a car accident that night.
Thanks.
All right, then.
There was military involvement
in both cases?
Why did they take the other car?
What?
- Damn it.
- Get your tools!
Hurry! Go!
A tow truck came
when the firefighters put out the fire.
And the tow truck just took that car.
Apparently, he took the damaged car
and drove toward Hanbal Mountain.
There's nothing
on the other car or the driver.
No idea whether they're alive or dead.
But the other car is more at fault.
What? Why is this open?
What?
Is that a frog?
Hey, sort it out.
Darn it!
I can't do anything
when it won't even turn on.
Do what?
Hey, it's the perfect time
for instant noodles.
Instant noodles sound good.
Yeah, let's have some before we continue.
- Is it still not turning on?
- No.
Damn it.
- How many?
- Three packs?
Three? Just for you?
VEOTIGO INSURANCE
Yes.
We're not done investigating yet.
Why are you still investigating?
The autopsy and funeral ended days ago!
We're doing our best.
Damn it, this is so frustrating.
BENEFICIARY DESIGNATION FORM
My sister still has to live
even if her husband died!
The woman with the baby who just left.
Her husband died
in the intersection accident.
She only ever buys products
that are on sale.
Her kid is too young for her to work.
Of course, I understand.
THE CONFIRMED BENEFICIARIES ARE
HIS WIFE, LEE SEO-HUI, AND HIS 2 CHILDREN
Yes, sir.
Kang, did you finish your report?
Soldiers came late that night
to clean up after the accident.
The street pub server
across the street saw it.
Soldiers? Man!
It'll get complicated
with soldiers in the equation.
Let's just close the case here.
I'll file an emergency request
for the life insurance payout.
They'll get the fund once it's approved.
No, there are some bad guys
who are eyeing that money.
So not yet. Just wait a bit.
Just a bit longer.
You were begging me
to speed things up the other day.
Hello?
- Is anyone home?
- We work hard.
So why can't you repay us?
If you borrowed money,
you have to repay it.
Huh? Don't you?
Hey, look around and see
if she has any money.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
- Stay here.
- Where's the money?
Hey, don't break anything.
Just look carefully, okay?
Yes, carefully.
Come on.
We don't want the whole town to know
she can't repay her debt.
Use the yellow crayon.
It's a sunflower, man.
With black in the middle.
- Are you colorblind?
- Hello, ma'am.
I'm Choi Kang
of the SIU unit.
I see.
I had to come to tell you something.
I'll just sit here.
Listen to me carefully, okay?
Once the inheritance process starts,
the beneficiaries take on
the deceased’s debts as well.
So, file a renunciation of inheritance
with the court.
But every beneficiary
must file the renunciation.
Now, would the renunciation prevent you
from taking the life insurance payout?
No.
Even if you renunciate inheritance,
you can get the life insurance payout,
as it's the beneficiary's own asset.
Even if debt collectors come to you,
demanding that you pay them back,
you can just ignore them.
What's that punk even saying?
Is he from an insurance company?
I think so, sir.
Remember what I told you
and do exactly that, okay?
Yes, thank you.
You must be So-yul.
You're so cute.
All right.
Eat something good with your mom.
And get some ice cream,
but don't share it with the baby, okay?
Yes, thank you.
What a damn beautiful sight.
Go and have some food.
Sure.
- I'll talk to them. Don't worry and go.
- Okay.
Get me some ice cream, too!
The twisty bar kind, okay?
Hey, insurance.
Come here.
Why are you interrupting our business?
Come here, you punk.
Just don't kill them.
Don't kill them.
Hey, you want to die?
How dare you ignore the boss--
You done writing it?
Yes, sir.
Table, 3,000,000 won.
Chairs, 2,000,000 won.
What kind of chair costs that much?
We have to get a whole new set to match.
The chairs look fine.
Yes, sir.
Next, 1,000,000 won for the coffee table.
That's a rip-off, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It's too cheap, isn't it?
No, sir.
You put your cigarette on the table?
Add 500,000 won for cleaning.
What? For cleaning?
That's how much it costs
to clean a home when moving in.
Write it down.
Yes, sir.
When you're done, write the date,
your name, and phone number, and sign it.
Give it to me.
Yes, sir.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
It's 6,500,000 won in total, right?
Yes.
Darn it, my pants.
Hey, add 7,000 won for dry cleaning.
Dry cleaning?
No, it's not what you think!
I'll just give you the 7,000 won now.
Hold on.
Here you go.
Listen, buddy.
I don't bully people into giving me money,
like you guys do,
so I'll only take the maximum legal rate
of 20 percent.
Pay me on time, okay?
Yes, sir.
- You're getting a call.
- Yes, sir.
That's my number, okay?
- Okay.
- Don't ignore it.
I'll text you my bank account number.
Yes, have a good day, sir.
I'll clean it up here. Have a good day.
SPECIAL MARTIAL ARTS YONGMU GYM
Have a great day, ma'am.
- Salute!
All right, see you tomorrow!
Do-yeon, show me your power!
Go!
Do-yeon!
Dad!
- Hello, sir!
- Hi.
You look great as always!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Do-yeon, let's say goodbye and go.
Salute!
See you tomorrow, Do-yeon.
Let's go.
Oh, sorry.
I think it's going to take some time.
Sure.
They even changed the login information
in that brief moment that night.
They're total pros.
Okay, I'm sure you can sort it out.
I trust you.
It's just that
there's a lot that I don't know.
I'm learning as I go.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
Okay, then.
- Bye, Do-yeon.
- Goodbye!
Hello, sir.
Hey, Do-yeon.
- Have you been good?
- Yes.
So, all is good?
Dad, what does that mean?
He's just asking how I'm doing.
All is well with you, too, little bro?
Of course, buddy.
Let's say goodbye to him and go.
Goodbye, sir.
Get home safely.
- Okay.
- Bye.
MAGNIFYING MEDIA
I was just about to talk about that.
We'll establish a strong security system
to prevent this from recurring
and install smart security cameras
- that can predict potential danger
- Does she take speech classes or what?
- and send alerts.
- She's all talk.
On top of that, I'll make sure
to hold people legally accountable...
VIDEO UPLOADED
...for the unfortunate incidents
that have recently happened...
Man.
Let's go home.
UNKNOWN: A NEW DAY IS COMING
MAMMOSEU MART
KIYUN BUS TERMINAL
- Hello.
- Good morning.
- The bus will leave in three minutes.
- Yes, sir.
#FIRST DAY TO WORK, #SUITED UP, #EXCITED,
#CAN'T WAIT FOR MY FIRST PAYCHECK
Crazy guy.
What a busy life.
THIRD EXPLOSION
ON AUG 22, 2025 AT 5:50 A.M.
We have a lot of deliveries this morning.
I made a list on the counter.
- Okay.
- I'll drop Min-seo off and be right over.
- Prepare the packages while I'm gone.
- Got it.
- Have a good day at school.
- Okay.
She's so cranky this morning.
She didn't even eat breakfast.
All because I won't buy her new sneakers.
Do you smell smoke?
Is someone burning something?
Anyway, drive safe.
Don't let your temper make you speed.
- What temper?
- What? I didn't say anything. See you.
If your grades improve
in the next midterm period,
I'll get you those crazy sneakers.
Really? You promise?
Really, Mom?
Of course. Have I ever lied?
Never mind if you don't want it.
Hey! You're making the van shake.
Gosh, are you that happy?
Yeah, totally.
Mom, say that again
so that I can record it.
What?
Come on. I'll listen to it
whenever I don't want to study.
My goodness.
Min-seo, it's me, your mom.
If your grades improve
in the next midterm season,
I'll buy those crazy 500,000-won sneakers
for you.
But you get nothing
if your grades drop, okay?
Promise.
Was there an accident or something?
Mom, I see firetrucks there.
That's the bus terminal, right?
Did the smoke smell come from there?
What happened?
Why have they blocked the road?
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
- How's the patient?
- He's unconscious.
Unconscious?
Careful.
UNIDENTIFIED MALE IN HIS 20S
ARMY18 8285
MAMMOSEU MART
All the Changri-dong leaders are here.
- Heading to work?
- Yes.
Are you having a serious discussion?
Don't even get us started.
A bus exploded. It's crazy.
What?
A bus exploded at the bus garage.
Did anyone get hurt?
No idea. We're just as in the dark.
Nobody won't tell us anything,
and it's not even on the news.
Oh, right.
You must know,
since you work for an insurance company.
Who are the first responders
when such an accident happens?
If it's a big one,
the police, ambulance, and firefighters.
Insurance company people also come.
See? That's normal.
What were soldiers doing there?
Soldiers?
I got a glimpse of the site
when I drove Min-seo to school
and saw military trucks.
Hello.
Even the Joint Chiefs
and the commander's lead car were there.
- Joint Chiefs and the commander?
- Yeah.
What do you mean?
There's Myeong-o's friend.
Min-seo's tutor.
Wait, I'll call him. I have his number.
Don't cry and stay put, okay?
- Ms. Lee?
- Yes.
What did she say?
Myeong-o left for work,
but she can't reach him.
He left early this morning
to catch the first bus.
I'm sure he's fine.
Hello, this is Min-seo's mom.
Have you talked to Myeong-o today,
by any chance?
There's been an accident,
and your son was...
Ma'am!
- Call the ambulance!
- Let's take my car.
- I got her!
- Okay!
Please help.
- Here we go.
- Pull yourself together!
So,
soldiers cleaned up the intersection
after the explosion,
and firefighters cleaned up
the ATM explosion in combat boots.
Now, when the bus terminal blew up,
the Joint Chiefs
and the commander's lead car came?
Yes.
And all three were explosions.
You said you saw ashy smoke
in the car crash at the intersection, too.
Su-il remembers it very clearly.
The same thing happened
in the ATM explosion.
Chun-bae saw the explosion this morning.
More ashy smoke.
A C-4.
It must've been a C-4.
Of course, it could be a modified bomb.
Ours again?
You sure?
This is driving me nuts.
I know you're in there.
Let's talk later.
Why the hell aren't you
picking up your damn phone?
Did you call?
Oh, you called a lot.
It's better to see you in person, anyway.
You kidding me?
Two people died in a bus explosion.
And one is barely hanging on in the ICU.
Lower your voice, will you?
You think this is your living room?
It just wouldn't be good
to have people outside hear us.
Have a seat.
What sneaky stuff
have you done behind my back
that we have something blowing off
every day?
And why is it my Kiyun-si, of all places?
Everyone's already making a big deal
about Sullivan pulling out
and making the plan
for the specialized zone become nothing!
You should be helping, not doing this!
You think I know what's going on?
This is a headache for me, too, okay?
I have to clean up the mess,
shush the prosecution and the police,
and stop the press!
I haven't even had time
for a sauna lately.
You know I've got a bad shoulder, right?
From getting tortured back in the day?
You're awfully good at keeping secrets
for someone who's shit at everything.
Why won't anyone tell me anything?
I'm asking you what's been exploding!
You're to become
the nation's leader one day!
Don't say stuff like "shit."
You're already on the same boat as I am.
I also went all-in on making Kiyun-si
a specialized tourism zone.
That's why I'm busy cleaning the mess
before everything falls apart.
Just tell me what's going on!
How am I supposed to know?
I'm still figuring it out too!
Minister Kim, are you sure
you don't know anything?
It's my responsibility
to clean up this mess, isn't it?
So leave it to me
and cut the bullshit, okay?
I'll kill you if you pull anything stupid
behind my back.
I ought to put a bullet
in that rude bitch.
Damn it.
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
MAY THE DECEASED REST IN PEACE
KIM MYEONG-O
They say people live up to their names.
You really are the strongest
when it comes to being nosy.
I can't believe you're going to a funeral
for someone you've never even met.
All the neighborhood leaders
knew him well.
My friend's friend is also my friend.
How could I turn a blind eye?
He was the only son of a single mother,
graduated from Hanguk University,
and spent three years working part-time
while looking for a job.
Then he finally got
a big corporate job recently.
It was his first day at work,
and he died on the way.
You make it sound
like he was your best friend.
I wasn't going to go this far,
but the bestie
of my bestie's bestie is also my bestie.
And you're my bestie for life,
- so you should--
- Enough.
Give a good amount of consolation money,
but not too much.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't go out.
Stay home with Do-yeon, okay?
If you need anything,
just let me get it for you, like always.
Okay, just go.
FUNERAL HALL 1
Did you say you need her permission?
- Of course, I do.
- Really?
Man, I used to feel so bad for Su-il
for having such a controlling wife,
but here you are, just like him.
Controlling? No, I'm just playing along.
You need her permission
to go to a funeral.
How's that playing along?
You're totally whipped.
You don't seem the type,
but you're surprisingly sharp.
What are these reporters
doing here anyway?
To interview the bereaved?
They're not asking anyone anything.
I guess a high-ranking official is here.
Let's go.
- She's here!
The only thing improving
is my acting these days.
All right, let's go.
- What's going on in Kiyun-si?
- Please tell us!
- What do you have to say?
- What happened?
- Please look this way!
- What's going on?
- Ma'am!
- What'll happen now?
Please let me pay my respects
before taking questions.
- What's the scale of the damage?
- How many casualties?
- Please tell us!
- What happens now?
- Please say something.
- Just one thing!
You must stay strong, ma'am.
I can't live on.
My son...
I can't live without my son.
My Myeong-o...
Please bring him back.
Myeong-o, take me with you!
Take me with you!
Ma'am.
I promise to investigate
the cause of Myeong-o's death.
Thank you so much. My Myeong-o...
Why are you here? What about the store?
I closed it for a bit
and came with Chun-bae.
I said we should work in shifts.
You couldn't even wait that long?
Don't be so cruel.
Closing your business for a few hours
for your dead neighbor isn't--
You think it's because of the money?
We're the only functioning grocery store
in the neighborhood.
I'm worried about those
who urgently need anything from the store.
Eat quickly and go.
Yeah, I don't have an appetite, anyway.
What a woman.
Why do you always use me as an excuse?
I came here alone.
Are you a bad friend, or just clueless?
Just eat your food.
FUNERAL HALL
I think we're done for the day now.
Come and eat some.
You haven't eaten all day.
I'm fine.
Ms. Lee needs you to stay strong
more than anyone right now.
You can't faint with her.
Come and have something to eat.
- Hey, Yong-hui.
- Hello.
Sorry, I'm late.
I had to close up the gym.
Go and greet Myeong-o.
Okay.
Myeong-o...
My goodness...
You haven't eaten, have you?
No, I ate. Stay seated.
This is Min-seo's tutor.
He's Myeong-o's friend.
Myeong-o introduced him to me.
And this is the manager
of Special Martial Arts Yongmu Gym.
He used to be
a close neighbor of Myeong-o.
I see. I'm Park Jeong-hwan.
I'm Lee Yong-hui.
You must be heartbroken.
Yes.
You know,
I still can't believe it.
None of us can.
Ms. Lee says she feels like
Myeong-o will come in any minute,
still in his suit, saying, "I'm home!"
I wish I could've seen him in his suit.
Here.
Oh, it's Myeong-o.
- My gosh.
- Look at him.
Our Myeong-o suited up nicely for work.
He even wore a tie and everything.
I know, gosh.
Oh, would you like something?
I just need to use the bathroom.
Okay.
There's a stuffed bunny.
A gift for someone?
This one's a video.
It must be so nice to start the day
with a surprise gift like that.
What's wrong, Yong-hui?
I need to go.
What's with him?
Byeong-nam!
What?
- You know the bunny?
- What about them?
The bus was on the bunny!
What are you talking about?
Wake up! How could a bus be on a...
- A bunny?
- Yes!
There was a stuffed bunny
sitting on the bus!
- How do you know?
- Myeong-o took a video of it.
- Can I see it? Let's see.
- Yes!
THIS IS A PRIVATE ACCOUNT
It's private.
What? Where is it?
I don't follow Myeong-o
on social media, so...
- Come on, how can we see it?
- How did you see it?
At the funeral hall.
On Myeong-o's friend's phone.
Excuse me.
Could we see Myeong-o's post from earlier?
- This thing, right?
- Right.
The stuffed bunnies at the recycling area
also had a sweet and oily scent.
What do you mean?
The C-4.
What?
A bomb?
What do you mean?
You left after looking at these photos.
What's going on?
Oh, I mean...
Just tell me everything.
This is my friend we're talking about.
There seems to have been
a bomb on the bus.
Who would've put it there?
Who would've done that?
It's dangerous, so we'll sort it--
No.
I...
I want to find
the bastard
behind all this.
SPECIAL MARTIAL ARTS YONGMU GYM
Good, but tilt it up a bit.
Thanks for working so hard in the heat.
- Please be thorough.
- Yes, of course.
Okay.
I keep my promises.
We're installing smart AI security cameras
to ensure safety
for the Changri-dong residents.
I know you must be so worried.
Of course.
How can there be so many accidents
in Changri-dong nonstop?
I'll make sure accidents like this
never happen again.
- Thank you.
These are getting set up
in front of schools too, right?
What a joke. Fussing over cameras
after everything's already happened.
Honey, she might hear you.
I don't care if she does.
Actually, I hope she hears me.
They're going to monitor us with those.
Hey, bad news for you.
Even Choi Kang, the man of no comments,
can't escape all those cameras, can you?
You want to bet
on whether I can escape them or not?
I'll bet 500 won that I can't.
You bet that I can, little bro.
Stay right here, okay?
I'll bring a gun right over
and actually shoot you.
You're too gullible.
- What?
- It's so much fun to tease you.
Stop it.
I told you to stop.
Hey, I'm telling you, cut it out.
Stop. I'm getting my gun.
Online security cameras. That's great.
Why? You can't hide from those?
That's not it. If that's online,
the satellite computer guys
must be watching them, too.
But what would you know?
So what? What are you going to do?
Play along, of course.
Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy. They are.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
- Wait. One, two, three.
- Three.
- Yeah, you jerks. Take this.
- Take this.
- You little rats.
Take this, too.
- Keep going.
- Take this. Come on.
One, two, three, go!
HEROES NEXT DOOR
It seems to have something to do
with the explosions in Kiyun-si.
THEY'RE LISTENING, SHUSH
Why are you telling me all this?
WHAT IF WE USE IT AGAINST THEM?
I brought something from Unit 203.
The computer signal disconnected
at the police station,
so these guys will go there.
What are you guys plotting?
People in our neighborhood are dying.
We need to do something.
A bomb threat in Kiyun-si?
- Stay back.
- Let me through.
Arrest them right now
and interrogate them.
Who are you?
How did you know about this place?
Subtitle translation by Min-sun Kim